Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXXIII is arranged in 21 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXXIII. PENSIONS
  - Sub-Series 407-0. Pensions
    - General. Report on Contributory Retirement Plans on Class I Railroads, 1949 (Box 534, Folder 15-17)
      1949 November 8
    - General. Company-Union Agreement and Unilateral Pension Systems, United States Railroad Retirement Board, 1951 (Box 534, Folder 18)
      1951 March
    - General. Replies to Circular Letter of November 1, 1956 Requesting Supplemental Retirement Plans, 1956-1957 (Box 534, Folder 19-21)
    - General, 1959 (Box 534, Folder 22)
      January-July 1959.
    - General, 1955-1958 (Box 534, Folder 23)
    - General, 1950-1954 (Box 534, Folder 24)
      September 1950-54.
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 534, Folder 25)
      September 1949-August 1950.
    - General, 1933-1949 (Box 534, Folder 26)
      1933-August 1949.
    - General. Reports, 1926-1941 (Box 534, Folder 27)
    - General, 1930 (Box 534, Folder 28)
    - General, 1931 (Box 534, Folder 29)
    - General, 1930-1931 (Box 534, Folder 30)
    - General, 1922-1930 (Box 534, Folder 31)
    - General, 1929 (Box 535, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 407-1. Pensions
    - Railway Express Agency, 1933 (Box 535, Folder 2)
    - Railway Express Agency, 1929-1930 (Box 535, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 407-2. Pensions
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, 1927 (Box 535, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 407-3. Pensions
    - Southern Railway, 1929 (Box 535, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 407-4. Pensions
    - St. Louis Southwestern Railroad, 1929 (Box 535, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 407-5. Pensions
    - Wabash Railroad, 1930 (Box 535, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 407-6. Pensions
    - Milwaukee Employees Pension Association, 1930 (Box 535, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 407-7. Pensions
    - Chicago and Northwestern Railroad, 1929-1946 (Box 535, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 407-8. Pensions
    - Federal Old Age Pension, 1930-1953 (Box 535, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 407-9. Pensions
    - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1930 (Box 535, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 407-10. Pensions
    - Grand Lodge, 1931-1952 (Box 535, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 407-11. Pensions
    - American Association for Old Age Security, 1931 (Box 535, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 407-12. Pensions
    - Illinois Central, 1933-1953 (Box 535, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 407-13. Pensions
    - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1936-1957 (Box 535, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 407-14. Pensions
    - Rock Island Railroad, 1940-1948 (Box 535, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 407-15. Pensions
    - Erie Railroad, 1948 (Box 535, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 407-16. Pensions
    - Civil Service Retirement and Disability Fund, 1954-1959 (Box 535, Folder 18)
      May 25, 1954-59.
    - Civil Service Retirement and Disability Fund, 1949-1954 (Box 535, Folder 19)
      1949-May 24, 1954.
  - Sub-Series 407-17. Pensions
    - Santa Fe Railroad, 1954 (Box 535, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 407-18. Pensions
    - Newburgh and South Shore Railway, 1957 (Box 535, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 407-19. Pensions
    - Lake Terminal Railroad, 1957 (Box 535, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 407-20. Pensions
    - River Terminal Railway Company, 1958 (Box 535, Folder 23)